{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20NBA%20player%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20points%20scored%20in%20a%20single%20game%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Wilt%20Chamberlain",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Michael%20Jordan",
        "Kobe%20Bryant",
        "LeBron%20James"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20team%20won%20the%20the%20NBA%20Championship%20in%202008%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Boston%20Celtics",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Los%20Angeles%20Lakers",
        "Chicago%20Bulls",
        "Golden%20State%20Warriors"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20youngest%20player%20to%20score%2050%20points%20in%20an%20NBA%20game%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Devin%20Booker",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "LeBron%20James",
        "Kobe%20Bryant",
        "Kevin%20Durant"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20NBA%20player%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20career%20triple-doubles%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Russell%20Westbrook",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Magic%20Johnson",
        "LeBron%20James",
        "Oscar%20Robertson"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20NBA%20team%20won%20the%20first-ever%20NBA%20championship%20in%201947%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Philadelphia%20Warriors",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Boston%20Celtics",
        "Minneapolis%20Lakers",
        "Chicago%20Stags"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20tallest%20player%20to%20ever%20play%20in%20the%20NBA%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Gheorghe%20Muresan",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Yao%20Ming",
        "Manute%20Bol",
        "Shawn%20Bradley"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20NBA%20player%20has%20the%20nickname%20'The%20Answer'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Allen%20Iverson",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tracy%20McGrady",
        "Shaquille%20O%27Neal",
        "Steve%20Nash"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20NBA%20player%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20three-pointers%20made%20in%20a%20single%20game%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Klay%20Thompson",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stephen%20Curry",
        "Ray%20Allen",
        "James%20Harden"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20year%20was%20the%20NBA%20founded%3F",
      "correct_answer": "1946",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1950",
        "1947",
        "1949"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20holds%20the%20record%20for%20the%20most%20NBA%20MVP%20awards%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Kareem%20Abdul-Jabbar",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Michael%20Jordan",
        "LeBron%20James",
        "Magic%20Johnson"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
